driversepson.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

We belong to all the drivers and software manufacturers. After you install the downloaded files for viruses. Our system(webpage) is not responsible for problems that may have downloaded the files to your computer.

**Collection and use of information**  
In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

**Use of cookies**  / When you visit www.driversepson.com, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user account details, preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, www.driversepson.com features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

**Log information**  / When you use www.driversepson.com, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

**Information Security**  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

**Data integrity**  
Drivers Epson processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

**Changes To Policy**  
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

**Advertising Privacy Policy**

driversepson.com use Google Adsens ads network.. This network has used cookies to [DoubleClick Dart](http://www.driversepson.com/download/aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nb29nbGUuY29tL2RvdWJsZWNsaWNrLw==) for Google Publishers’s web sites. Google ,used this cookies for publish to ads of Advertiser’s as3 th. Part seller. Using this section, pusblish the ads which of the thesame as like to content around the Internet. Visit to [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.driversepson.com/download/aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nb29nbGUuY29tL3BvbGljaWVzL3ByaXZhY3kvYWRzLw==), you can suspend the DART cookies how to make it.

When the Google visit our web sites, use 3th part ads network ( etc. Adnet, Adcash … ) services fort this. This Ads Networks; use your personal informations ( name, address, email or gsm numbers ) for the their services; view ads to visitors interested to products and service around the internet.

For all this to, Privacy Policy and Rules which of used the Networks, you can download or read atteched file [NAI Self- Regulatory Principles For Publishers ( PDF )](http://www.driversepson.com/download/aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uZXR3b3JrYWR2ZXJ0aXNpbmcub3JnL3NpdGVzL2RlZmF1bHQvZmlsZXMvaW1jZS9wcmluY2lwbGVzLnBkZg==)
